<resources>
    <string name="app_name">London Tour Guide</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main2">Main2Activity</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main3">Main3Activity</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main">MainActivity</string>

    <string name="nav_menu_information_option">Information</string>
    <string name="nav_menu_map_option">Map</string>

    <string name="london_description">
        London, the capital of England and the United Kingdom,
        is a 21st-century city with history stretching back to Roman times.
        At its centre stand the imposing Houses of Parliament, the iconic ‘Big Ben’
        clock tower and Westminster Abbey, site of British monarch coronations.
        Across the Thames River, the London Eye observation wheel provides panoramic
        views of the South Bank cultural complex, and the entire city.
    </string>

    <string name="fun_facts">
1.	It is illegal to die in the Palace of Westminster.  \n
2.	More languages are spoken in London that in any other city in the world. The total is over 300.  \n
3.	London has more universities in the world top 40 universities list than any other city. There are four.  \n
4.	It is considered an act of treason to put a postage stamp with the queen’s head upside down on an envelope!  \n
5.	Big Ben is not actually the name of the clock, it is the name of the bell which is inside the clock.  \n
6.	In 1945, a flock of birds landed on the minute hand of Big Ben and put the time back by 5 minutes.  \n
7.	The world’s first subway was built in London in 1863.  \n
8.	In 2008, the name Muhammad became the most popular for newborn boys in London.  \n
9.	London is the first of the world’s major cities in 2010 that imposed restrictions on the movement speed of … pedestrians.  \n
10.	Unusual street names in London include Ha Ha Road in Greenwich, Hooker’s Road in Walthamstow, Quaggy Walk in Blackheath, and Cyclops Mews in Limehouse.  \n
11.	There’s a sign on the Chelsea Embankment and Albert Bridge that orders marching troops to break their step as the cross, so the vibrations don’t damage the structure.  \n
12.	To pass the Knowledge, the insanely difficult London geography test required of black-cab drivers in the city, you must master 320 basic routes, all of their 25,000 streets, and many landmarks.  \n
13.	Karl Marx drafted the Communist Manifesto in a room above the Red Lion pub on Great Windmill Street. It’s now a trendy B@1 bar.  \n
14.	In 1647, Christmas was abolished by the English Parliament. No-one was allowed to celebrate.
    </string>

    <string name="source1">
        https://friendlylocalguides.com/blog/25-fun-facts-about-london
    </string>
    <string name="source2"></string>
    <string name="source3"></string>
</resources>
